

Profile

UX/UI design-thinking, responsive web design, and creation are my passions. Delighting users by creating web applications that are inspiring, engaging, and memorable is what drives me and motivates me to do more. Experienced in Front-End and Back-End Technologies. I am extremely passionate about approaching programming and design challenges from different angles and collaborating with others to create value-driven web applications and products that delight users and keep them coming back. Being part of a fast-paced, quality-driven team building products that drive true value and increase user-adoption are truly inspiring to me.

Employment History

Lead UX/UI Designer, LingoLabs, Washington, D.C.

FEBRUARY 2020 - PRESENT

- Gathering and evaluating user requirements, in collaboration with product managers and engineers.
- Illustrating design ideas using storyboards, process flows and sitemaps
- Designing graphic user interface elements, like menus, tabs, widgets as well as many other UI components.
- · Building navigation components.
- Build page navigation buttons and search fields.
- Develop UI mock-ups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function, look, and feel like.
- Create original graphic designs (e.g.: images, sketches, and tables)
- Prepare and present rough drafts to internal teams and key stakeholders.
- Identify and troubleshoot UX problems (e.g. responsiveness)
- Conduct layout adjustments and changes based on user feedback.
- Adhere to style standards and branding look and feel.
- Utilizing design software and wireframe tools such as FIGMA.
- Strong communication skills.

Manager, Nazca Mochica Peruvian Cuisine, Washington, D.C.

OCTOBER 2016 - JANUARY 2020

- Coordinating daily restaurant management operations
- Overseeing the delivery of superior foods and beverages and maximizing customer service and satisfaction
- Identifying new business models to generate new revenue streams for clients in the digital economy.
- Responding efficiently and accurately to customer requirements and/or complaints
- Responsible for leading all the aspects of the business and delivering high-quality menus, products, and services.
- POS and Software maintenance
- Responsible for maintaining and increasing revenues
- Motivating, training and mentoring staff
- Ensuring efficient restaurant operations, as well as maintaining high levels of production, productivity, and customer-service standards
- Leveraged management skills and optimized both the front and back of the house by implementing software and new workflows

Details

Arlington, 22201, United States (202)210-9355

Nikola4work@gmail.com

Links

My Portfolio

GitHub

LinkedIn

Skills

Responsive web design

Project Management

Wire Frame Design - FIGMA

Front-end and back-end web development

UX/UI Design Thinking

Excellent & Engaging communicator

Languages

Serbian

Span<u>ish</u>

English

Technologies

HTML | CSS | Figma | Bootstrap JavaScript | jQuery | Node.js React.js | MongoDB | MySQL

- Regularly reviewed product quality and researched the market place for alternative and better vendors and service providers
- Appraise staff performance, provided feedback and devised training and mentoring to ensure continued improvement and professional development
- Estimated future revenues, areas of growth and revenue models
- Controlled and oversee operational costs
- Promoted the brand using social platforms and other marketing channels

General Manager, 1209 N Taft Street LLC, Arlington, V.A

NOVEMBER 2014 - PRESENT

- Implement financial and operational initiatives to increase profitability and cut costs
- Inspect facilities and implemented maintenance programs and schedules
- Negotiate leases, contracts and advised on changes related to amendments in policy
- Project management of renovations, contractors and maintenance work
- Evaluate market conditions and prices when undertaking new contractual agreements
- Research and investigated service providers conducted back round searches on new tenants prior to executing contracts and located reliable insurance firms
- Identify opportunities and developed strategies to enhance the financial performance of the properties
- Conduct marketing and outreach campaigns to attract new lessees and tenants

Education

Full Stack Web Development, George Washington University, Arlington, V.A OCTOBER 2019 – MAY 2020

Bachelor's of Science in AOS Operations Systems, Union – Nikola Tesla, Belgrade, Serbia

2018 - PRESENT

Bachelor's Degree in Marketing, Higher Business School of Professional Studies, Belgrade, Serbia

2012 - 2015